

www

https://loouislow81.github.ic

nhone

(06) 016 4010 45/

email

loouis@gmail.com



LOOUISLOW

UI/UX DESIGNER SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PRELUDE

I am influenced with freestyle art and codes, I am a person addicted in codes, art & music and it wis so bloody complicated that i don't know how to be a nice guy. They still don't get it what i mean, I remain calm and didn't want to quarrel, I'll be getting silence... Everything began with, when I have found myself true maps to enter world of codes, making a lot of friends over the widest internet, fu coding with interesting people I met.

I worked with several startups as a freelance developer. I built Web services and apps using open source technologies and frameworks such as Python and JavaScript, Backbone js, NodeJs. I built apps: Uls with cutting edge technologies like HTML/Pug/Jade and CSS/Sass. This allowed me to learn how to work independently, communicate with clients, personal accounting and gain a mastery is median development tools.

HOBB

Reading usually. Console Gaming and DIY embedded prototypes. I make some progressive music as well. Check out my recent tracks at •• SoundCloud. Would you be so kind please leave your comment there. Thanks.

EXPERIENCE

13 VEARS EXPERIENCE



DOGSBARK

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

ARCHITECT

LEISURE REMOTE CANADA

2004 - 2017

Embedded Design, Prototyping and Architect. Machine Learning. Design and development o integration test strategies. Debugging and Security Audits. Well documentation.



GOODY

CUETIVIA DE ENICINIEED

FRONT END

FULLTIME IN HOUSE MALAYSIA

Craft from scratch front and back-end UI. UI FX without JS. Material designs with Adobe Photoshop. Convert from PSD to CSS. Created L boilerplate using with API services. Create UI outstop library and devices!



INTERNET MASTERMIND

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

FRONT END

FULL TIME IN HOUSE MALAYSIA

2014 - 2015

Implement UI and UX for marketing related applications with Bootstrap UI framework. Frontend and backend UI prototyping (web, app). Custom web design with WordPress.



JPRINT STUDIO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

FRONT END

FULL TIME IN HOUSE MALAYSIA

2012 2012

Implement web-based platform for convertible web, project management and e-commerce. Plar and manage the web business and development affairs.



INFO KINETICS

SYSTEM ADMIN

WIDE RANGE

FULLTIME (IN HOUSE) N
2010 - 2012

Backup Strategy, Recovery Disaster planning and deployments. Virtualization deployment client and server by using Microsoft Virtual PC. System Infrastructure planning, design, Data modeling and Security deployments.



ALTERA

OFTWARE ENGINEER

DIGITAL SIGNAL

PART TIME REMOTE MALAYSIA

2006 - 2010

Assisting in software development activities including implementing assigned tasks/modules and performing software guality assurance for engineering software solutions. Aiding in softwar maintenance activity supporting internal engineering community.

SKILLS

JUST MY AWESOME SKILLS



EMBEDDED SYSTEM



API DEVELOPMENT Advanced, 6 years



NEURAL NETWORK DEVELOPMENT 96%

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT Expert, 11 years

KNOWLEDGI

Debian	C/C++	NodeJS	Python
Bash	Bootstrap	HTML/Pug	CSS/Sass
Adobe PS	Adobe Al	Material Design	Docker
AngularJS	MongoDB	Machine Learning	Steinberg Cubase
Propellerh. Reason	Embedded System		

SKILL BALANC



LANGUAGE SKILLS

EDUCATION

JUST MY EDUCATIO

I always believe experience is more important than what kind of education you have learne



SHREWSBURY COLLEGE
VISUAL ART & DESIGN

I also am artist. I gave myself a chance to stell into a little bit deeper into the art. Also, I am a perfectionist either in I II or I IX



UNIVERSITY OF MANCHESTER

E & E ENGINEERING

(B.DEGREE UK)
2002 - 2005

I was always wanting to be an inventor like robotic, anything since I was a little kid. But, well they all came true. I just kept doing it. Never stop



CHUNG LING HIGH SCHOOL

Just an ordinary student not very fond of school subjects, beside the computer programming and science classes. Never a good chance in Art class.

